{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113963723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113963723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" b943a827-8712-48f7-aa79-4793b7e1b838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113968989","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113968988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" b943a827-8712-48f7-aa79-4793b7e1b838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113974925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113974925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" b943a827-8712-48f7-aa79-4793b7e1b838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113977586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113977586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" b943a827-8712-48f7-aa79-4793b7e1b838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113995730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113995729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 36885956-2aec-4cc8-aed6-a71523a1b0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549113997836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549113997835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 36885956-2aec-4cc8-aed6-a71523a1b0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114011360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114011360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 36885956-2aec-4cc8-aed6-a71523a1b0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114027324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114027324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114043611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114043610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114046294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114046294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114063256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114063256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114065659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114065659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114074464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114074463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114087030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114087030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114093011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114093011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114105344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114105344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114108729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114108729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114118015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114118013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114118234","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114118234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114128294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114128294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549114134524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549114134524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_162548"," gameId":" 5ac906c9-ae55-46b0-ad6a-2a5380170deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}